onbile.com 2013-06-16

# Privacy Policy & Terms of Services

## ONBILE Privacy Policy

Last Updated on 6th February 2012

Thank you for visiting ONBILE. We take your privacy seriously and we are committed to honoring the privacy of our members and visitors. We will not sell, lease or exchange your personal data to, or otherwise share your personal data with, third parties in ways other than described in this Privacy Policy.

We provide this Privacy Policy, part of our overall Terms of Service, to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive when you visit www.onbile.com, and when you use any part of our service available through the site or other related websites, toolbars, widgets, applications or distribution channels we may operate from our "Service".

This Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Site or the Service, or when you access or use any content appearing on the Site or made available through the Service, or that we collect on your behalf as part of the Service. This Policy may be amended or updated from time to time.

If we make any material changes to this Policy, we will post a notice of these changes on our website and in this Policy.

You are advised to consult this Policy regularly for any changes. If you would like to be notified by email if and when material changes are made to this Policy, please send an email to [www.onbile.com/contact-us/](http://www.onbile.com/contact-us/)

  1. ### Information Collection & Use:

    1. **Registration**

Personally Identifiable Information: In the course of using the Service, we will ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you and administer your account ("Personal Information"), as well as enabling you to access certain restricted parts of the Site and the Service. Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, mailing address, email address, company name and URL.

ONBILE Service requires a Login in order to provide you with a personalized account. During our account registration process, we will collect a login name, password, and an email address from you. You must provide all of this information in order to obtain an account. After completing our registration form, you will receive a welcome email describing your new ONBILE account, and how to access that account. You may, at your option, also store your social edia credentials as a part of your account with our Service.

Non Personally Identifiable Information: When you access the Site or use the Service, we collect the following:

      * Information regarding your use of the Service, including, activity and visit behavior on your mobile website.
      * Information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website or online service "Log Data", that may include, but is not limited to your computer's Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page you were visiting before you came to the Site and information you search for on the Site.
      * Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use "persistent cookies" to save your username and login password for future logins to the Site. We use "session ID cookies" to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor web traffic routing on the Site and aggregate usage of the Service. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the website you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service.

Policy Towards Children: We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from minors. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at www.onbile.com/contact-us/

    2. **Account Subscriptions**

If you choose to continue service with ONBILE via a paid account, ONBILE will collect personally identifiable information (credit card number, billing address, phone number) and keep this information on file in our secure server in order to process your recurring invoices. This information is only used to verify credit card authenticity, and issue invoices as per your service agreement.

Upon discontinuation of ONBILE service, your information will be destroyed on our billing system. If we are unable to process your subscription for a given month, this information, along with your account information, may be used to contact you.

    3. **Tell-A-Friend Tools**

ONBILE provides a number of tools that will allow you to promote your website, like articles in your website, over email. Email addresses entered into these forms are not stored in our database, but may be stored in our system logs in text format to assist us in tracking down abusive users, or using these tools for spamming. We will never contact addresses logged in this manner. The email sent through any of these mechanisms is a one time email only.

    4. **Hosted websites**

Users hosting websites with ONBILE are given tools that may ask you optionally enter your email address when making comments on their website, or contacting them through their website. Since users on ONBILE can manipulate the HTML code on their site directly, there are opportunities available for a malicious user to inject code that would log your information before it reaches our system.

In addition, once in our system, website owners will have the opportunity to review and modify any information entered into their website. Since we do not have full control over how members run their individual sites, this privacy policy does not apply to any hosted ONBILE website that you do not own. You should check that you trust the owner of a particular website before submitting personally identifiable on that site.

    5. **Server Logs**

When accessing web pages on the ONBILE.COM domain, ONBILE may log your IP address, access URL, time of access, browser type, and referral URL in order to provide us with internal information regarding site traffic statistics. This information may also be used to identify users who are using the service for spam or other activity that is deemed in conflict with our Terms of Service. This information is used in the aggregate, and we never linked back to any personally identifiable information.

    6. **Third Party Websites**

This Policy applies only to the Service. We do not exercise control over websites that provide information, or over banners, other advertisements or links from within the Site or the Service. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information that you submit. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and other terms of the other websites.

The collection and use of such information and access of any third party websites are subject to such third party's privacy policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and other terms of such third parties' websites before using their services.

  2. ### How We Use Personal Information

Personal Information is used for the following purposes: (i) to provide the Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service and any accounts you may have with us, (iii) to personalize your experience, (iv) to provide to you service announcements, (v) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties that we believe you may find useful or interesting, such as newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, (vi) on behalf of and according to instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners, (vii) to enforce our Terms of Service, (viii) to resolve any disputes between users of the Site or between such users and us, and (ix) to contact you to obtain feedback from you regarding the Site and the Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such announcements, information or offers, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in the communication.

We use information that is not Personal Information for the above purposes and in addition in order to (i) monitor and analyze use of the Service and for the technical administration of the Site, (ii) improve the Site and the Service, (iii) generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and (iv) verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

ONBILE Website Manager interface will always give you an option before any piece of your personally identifiable information is presented on your website, and situations where information will be published is made clear in arious spots in the interface.

In addition, we may post additional ancillary privacy notices with respect to specific services. We don't send contact information unless the matter is deemed urgent, and most communication will occur through your ONBILE Website Manager Interface. We also may use your information to send you messages regarding new services or other products from ONBILE, but will not share this information with third parties for any marketing purposes.

Information collected our service logs is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding website traffic. This statistical information is not aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.

ONBILE, Llc is the sole owner of information collected on <http://www.onbile.com/>. Your information is never shared, leased or given to any third parties in ways other than disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

  3. ### Information Security

We store all user information in secure databases protected via a variety of industry-standard access controls. Secure passwords, SSL encryption, disk-based encryption, firewalls, and other measures are in place that helps us to protect your data. This data is accessed only for the purposes specified in this privacy statement.

If you have any questions about security on our website, you can review our hosting FAQ or send us a support request using our support system.

  4. ### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

    1. **Changing Information**

All information that ONBILE stores related to your account, including any subscription billing information, is accessible through your ONBILE Website Manager interface. You may use this interface to adjust your information at any time, and we encourage you to keep this information up to date so that your customer service requests and billing processes operate efficiently.

    2. **Removing Information**

To remove your personally identifiable information from our system, submit your account for deactivation. Your personal information will be removed immediately, though your actual login name will remain reserved on our system until re-collection. If you wish to only remove your billing subscription information, cancel your paid account. Both of these removals can be accessed through your ONBILE Website Manager interface.

  5. ### Communications from ONBILE, Llc.

    1. **Service-related Announcements**

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

    2. **Other Messages and Customer Service**

We may also send you messages from time to time about new features or services that we offer to our users. You may opt-out of these communications at any time by clicking on the link at the bottom of our communications to you, or by changing your preferences in your profile.

Upon issuing a customer support request to ONBILE, we may use your information and email address to contact you regarding your inquiry.

  6. ### Information Sharing and Disclosure

    1. **Aggregate Information Non Personally Identifiable**

We may share aggregated information, including reports generated as a result of your use of the Service that includes non-identifying information and Log Data, with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, other commercial purposes and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information. We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

    2. **Personally Identifiable Information**

ONBILE employs third-party service providers to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include credit card processing, email service providers, analyzing data, providing customer service. These service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for any other purposes.

In the event of a business transfer or sale by ONBILE, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the commitments made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, you consent otherwise).

We may release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Service; or protect the rights, property, or safety of ONBILE, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

    3. **Combined Information**

We may combine certain Personal Information with non Personal Information in order to allow us to create information packages and services that are better tailored to your interests and preferences. Among other things, linking this information may allow us generally to improve and personalize the Site and the Service. If we combine or link any information with your Personal Information, the resulting combination will be treated as Personal Information under this Policy.

    4. **Service Providers and Business Transfers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on our behalf and to perform services related to administration of the Service or the Site (including, without limitation, maintenance, payments, hosting and database management services, web analytics and administration). These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated to comply with this Policy.

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our assets, including among others your Personal Information and Log Data, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of all or substantially all of our shares or assets, or in the event of our bankruptcy.

    5. **Disclosure by you of information of other users**

The sending of unwanted messages from one user to another is strictly forbidden. Personal Information of another user obtained through your use of the Site or the Service may be used by you only for the purpose for which such information was provided to you and strictly in accordance with the Terms of Service and this Policy, or otherwise subject to such user's prior written consent. Your information may be processed, maintained or transferred outside of your state, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

    6. **Your Submissions**

Any information you choose to provide in a comment or a submission on the Site or the Service will be publicly available and should reflect how much you want other users to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage you to think carefully about what information about yourself you disclose in your comments or submissions. If you disclose your Personal Information to others, whether or not they are users of the Site, on our Site or through the Service or otherwise, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them.

    7. **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect our or a third party's property and rights, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable.

  7. ### Changing or Deleting Your Information

Our users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information, if not required to be retained by law or for legitimate business reasons. If you completely delete all such information, your account may be deactivated.

In addition, we may delete any information provided by you or related to you, pursuant to our policies as then in effect.

  8. ### Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

  9. ### Cookies

Like most websites, we use small bits of data called cookies stored on users' computers to simulate a continuous connection. Cookies let us 'remember' information about your preferences and passwords and allow you to move within our Service without reintroducing yourself. Members who disable cookies will not be able to use the Service, as they are required to maintain your login to our service within a browser session.

Disabling cookies does not prevent you from accessing websites published under our system, though some features of those sites may be degraded.

These cookies can be tied back to personally identifiable information only in the event that you are logged in to our Service. If you are logged in to our Service, the cookies on your computer will uniquely identify your account within our system.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by ONBILE only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. See the 'Third Party Advertisers' section for more details.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See Third Party Advertisers.

  10. ### Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms/Member Websites

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, or on any ONBILE member website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

Certain information, such as your name and IP address are logged by our system when posting messages, and are made available to the owner of the website you are posting on. These items may be displayed to readers of the site you are posting on, depending on the settings of that particular site. If you would not like to have these details disclosed, refrain from posting messages to any ONBILE bulletin board or chat room.

  11. ### Links to Other Sites

This website contains links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed.

This links to other sites are not owned or controlled by ONBILE. Please be aware that we, ONBILE, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this Website.

  12. ### Business Transitions, International Processing or Transfer

Your information may be processed, maintained or transferred outside of your state, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

In the event ONBILE goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

  13. ### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

  14. ### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice within your ONBILE Website Manager interface.

  15. ### Security

We are concerned with safeguarding your information. We employ a variety of measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access and disclosure. However, we do not promise that your Personal Information or private communications will be protected from unauthorized disclosure or use. PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY PRIVILEGED INFORMATION ON THE SITE OR WHEN USING THE SERVICE.

If you receive an e-mail asking you to update your Personal Information, do not reply and please contact us at [www.onbile.com/contact-us/](http://www.onbile.com/contact-us/)

  16. ### Contacting Us

If you have any concerns or questions about this Policy, please contact us at [www.onbile.com/contact-us/](http://www.onbile.com/contact-us/).

**ONBILE is located at:**

    * **Onbile, S.L. (EUROPE-EU)**
      * Av.Marqués de Sotelo 1 Pta.3 - 46002 Valencia - SPAIN
      * Av.Cortes Valencianas, 26 Bloque I, Esc.1, Oficina 2 - 46015 Valencia – SPAIN
    * **Onbile, Llc. (USA)**
      * 228 Hamilton Ave. 3rd Floor, Palo Alto, CA 94301 - USA

Copyright © 2012, ONBILE, LLC. All rights reserved.
